<odoo>

    <template id="city_manager_approval_letter">
        <div style="font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; line-height: 1.5;">

            <p>
                The City Manager in accordance with the System of Delegations of the CCT, 
                Section 9(1) of the City Manager’s delegated authority, authorised an investigation
                into allegations of Unauthorised, Irregular or Fruitless and Wasteful (UIFW)
                expenditure and the mismanagement of funds.
            </p>

            <p>
                To further the investigation, it is required to obtain access to the available email
                and OneDrive accounts for the following staff member:
            </p>

            <ul>
                <t t-foreach="suspect_ids" t-as="supect">
                    <li><t t-out="supect.name"/> for the period <t t-out="date_from"/> to <t t-out="date_to"/></li>
                </t>
            </ul>

            <p>
                It should be noted that EFS’ search criteria are limited to the email accounts of the
                staff member listed above and to determining whether:
            </p>

            <ul>
                <li><t t-esc="allegation_nature_id"/></li>
            </ul>

            <p>
                EFS’s search criteria will include, <i>inter alia</i>, the following terms, and/or variations 
                thereof:
            </p>

            <p>
                EFS will utilise both the Microsoft Purview eDiscovery, as well as the Discovery 
                Accelerator platforms to apply the above searches and review the electronically 
                stored information that falls within the specified search criteria, in accordance with
                the authorisation granted.
            </p>
            
            <p>
                In terms of the System of Delegations, approved by Council on 30 July 2025 (item 
                C26/07/25), Part 28: (B) Section 25(10)(b), the City Manager in the performance of 
                his functions and, <i>“Subject to any relevant legislation, have access to, to copy 
                and/or to seize any register, file, document, account, minute and/or other records, 
                whether physical or electronic, of the City and/or any such register, file, document 
                and/or record which may be maintained by any employee, in relation to the 
                performance of his/her official functions.”</i>
            </p>
            
            <p>
                Under cover of this memorandum, please find for your review and signature a 
                memorandum addressed to Mr Andre Stelzner, Chief Digital Officer: Information 
                Systems and Technology, for his information and necessary action.
            </p>

            <p>
                Feel free to contact me with any related comments/ queries.
            </p>

        </div>
    </template>




    <template id="chief_digital_officer_approval_letter">
        <div style="font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; line-height: 1.5;">
            
            <p>
                I, the City Manager, in accordance with the System of Delegations of the CCT, 
                Section 9(1) of the City Manager’s delegated authority, authorised an investigation 
                into allegations of Unauthorised, Irregular or Fruitless and Wasteful (UIFW) 
                expenditure and the mismanagement of funds.
            </p>

            <p>
                To further the investigation, it is required to obtain access to the available email 
                and OneDrive accounts for the following staff member:
            </p>

            <ul>
                <t t-foreach="suspect_ids" t-as="supect">
                    <li><t t-out="supect.name"/> for the period <t t-out="date_from"/> to <t t-out="date_to"/></li>
                </t>
            </ul>

            <p>
                In terms of the System of Delegations, approved by Council on 30 July 2025 (item 
                C26/07/25), Part 28: (B) Section 25(10)(b), the City Manager in the performance of 
                his functions and, <i>“Subject to any relevant legislation, have access to, to copy 
                and/or to seize any register, file, document, account, minute and/or other records, 
                whether physical <strong>or electronic</strong>, of the City and/or any such register, file, 
                document and/or record which may be maintained by any employee, in relation to 
                the performance of his/her official functions”.</i>
            </p>

            <p>
                EFS will utilise both the Microsoft Purview eDiscovery as well as the Discovery 
                Accelerator platforms to apply the above searches and review the electronically 
                stored information that falls within the specified search criteria, in accordance with 
                the authorisation granted.
            </p>

            <p>
                You are accordingly hereby authorised to provide the requested information to 
                Mr Investigator Name, Senior Forensic Officer, Ethics and Forensic Services, Office 
                of the City Manager.
            </p>

        </div>
    </template>

</odoo>