<odoo>

    <template id="line_auth_letter">
        <div style="font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; line-height: 1.5;">

            <p>
                The schedule contains allegations received by the Ethics and Forensic Services department and our 
                recommendations in respect thereof, which is submitted for your approval to be referred to the relevant 
                line directorates in accordance with the sections 8.11.4 and 8.11.5 of the Fraud Prevention Policy and 
                Response Plan as well as the applicable Executive Directors delegations.
            </p>

            <p>
                These allegations are untested and the following matters are herewith forwarded to you for your 
                consideration and approval for onward submission to the relevant line directorates:
            </p>

            <p>
                1. <t t-esc="line_refrence"/>
            </p>

            <p>
                Feel free to contact me with any related comments/queries.
            </p>

           

        </div>
    </template>

    <template id="forensic_auth_letter">
        <div style="font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; line-height: 1.5;">

            <p>
               The schedule contains allegations received by the Ethics and Forensic Services department 
               and our recommendations in respect thereof, which is submitted for authorisation in terms 
               of section 9(1) of your delegated authority as read in the City’s System of Council Delegations. 

 
            </p>

            <p>
                These allegations are untested and the following forensic matter is herewith 
                forwarded to you for further consideration and authorisation. 

            </p>

            <p>
                1. <t t-esc="line_refrence"/>
            </p>

            <p>
                Feel free to contact me with any related comments/queries.
            </p>




        </div>
    </template>

    <template id="preliminary_auth_letter">
        <div style="font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; line-height: 1.5;">

        
            <p>
                As per the schedule meeting dated 3 March 2025, 
                a request for preliminary assessment has been 
                recommended by the Ethics and Forensic Services Recommendation Committee.
                These allegations are untested and a preliminary assessment is necessary 
                to determine whether a full forensic investigation is required: 

 
            </p>

            <p>
                1. <t t-esc="line_refrence"/>
            </p>

        

        </div>
    </template>

    <template id="lifestyle_auth_letter">
        <div style="font-family: Arial; font-size: 15px; line-height: 1.5;">

            <p>
                The City Manager is vested with an implied power to authorise lifestyle
                reviews to mitigate and detect risks associated with fraud, corruption, 
                maladministration and / or unethical conduct.
 
            </p>
            <p>
                In the annual Strategic Management Framework (SMF) it was recommended 
                in the Finance Directorate section that lifestyle audits should be completed 
                for all officials who are involved in SCM processes. The implementation and 
                roll out is also tracked and monitored on the CCT Corporate Risk Register 
                (CCTCRR) with a project end date of 31 December 2026.
            </p>

            <p>
                Authority is hereby requested to conduct 
                lifestyle reviews on the newly appointed 
                SCM Managers and Heads within Supply Chain Management, Finance directorate.
            </p>

            <p>
                Feel free to contact me with any related comments/queries.
            </p>

        </div>
    </template>
</odoo>